[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the comedy Trading Places, how much money does Clarence Beeks give Ophelia the prostitute to have her talk dirty to Louis Winthorpe in front of his fianc\u00e9e, Penelope?", "correct_answer": "$100", "incorrect_answers": ["$20", "$500", "$50"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1920 Edward P. Eddie Eagan won the first Olympic boxing gold medal for the USA. In 1932, he won a second gold Olympic medal in which sport?", "correct_answer": "Bobsledding", "incorrect_answers": ["Wrestling", "Greco-Roman Wrestling", "The Shot Put"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1995 movie do we find the character played by Nicholas Cage literaly drinking himself to death?", "correct_answer": "Leaving Las Vegas", "incorrect_answers": ["Stepmom", "National Security", "City of Angels"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These substances, present in some essential oils, slow down the development of bacteria.", "correct_answer": "Bacteriostatic", "incorrect_answers": ["Bacterising", "Bacteriostopping", "Bactericidal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is an existing country, recognized by the United Nations?", "correct_answer": "North Korea", "incorrect_answers": ["North Vietnam", "North Cyprus", "North Africa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "USA boycotted the 1980 Summer Olympics held in what city?", "correct_answer": "Moscow", "incorrect_answers": ["Tehran", "Beijing", "Prague"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the term for the points in the lunar cycle when the tides range is minimal?", "correct_answer": "Neap Tide", "incorrect_answers": ["Ebb Tide", "Adoble Tide", "Perigean Tide"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "William Friedkin directed several art films after Good Times, including the Golden Globe-nominated film version of this off-Broadway play written by Mart Crowley.", "correct_answer": "The Boys in the Band", "incorrect_answers": ["Cry for Us All", "Rizzo", "The Me Nobody Knows"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Clocks made before 1687 had only one hand.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animal is the largest land predator?", "correct_answer": "Kodiak bear", "incorrect_answers": ["Elephant", "Giant anteater", "Man"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not a variety of the lemon tree?", "correct_answer": "California", "incorrect_answers": ["Lisbon", "Verna", "Lemonade"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the largest carnivorous mammal endemic to the island of Madagascar?", "correct_answer": "Fossa", "incorrect_answers": ["Short-tailed Mongoose", "Fanaloka", "Meerkat"]}]